[{"answer": "LINKEN: Well look there's two things going on here.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Do you agree with that statement Mr. Blinken, that when it comes to our national security intelligence isn't necessarily a fact?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "The intelligence community, no one's going to guarantee, use the word guarantee, they're going to tell you ...", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Can you guarantee that chemical weapons were used and they were used by the Assad regime?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Because we believe beyond a reasonable doubt, let me use that standard it's familiar to a lot of people, that beyond reasonable doubt that the Assad regime used chemical weapons against its own people.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Well if that's the basis for your attack why would you attack if you can't even guarantee the basis?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I'm still a no at this point, we're talking about going to war and if there is a clear and present danger to the United States then of course I want the President to act swiftly and decisively.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "You still a no?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Yeah, of course I'm going to keep an open mind, I'm leaning though, I want to hear the best intelligence that we have right up until the time we vote.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Representative Chaffetz?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Representative Hahn?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well those were horrible pictures, look I'm a mother, I'm a grandmother.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "When you see the pictures of those kids though, there's no crisis of conscience?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "It is and I think that it was said both by Secretary Rumsfeld and Tony Blinken not very well frankly.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "To hear that said to the American people, to hear that the burden of proof beyond a reasonable doubt, which we don't even like in criminal trials, let alone we're deciding to bomb, surprising to you?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "So intelligence still means that you know something?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "That's exactly right.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "We could take some comfort in that?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "But that's not what Mr. Rumsfeld said?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "That's not what Mr. Blinken was prepared to say?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Chris, our basis for what might be a military operation is absolutely solid.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Is your basis for attack solid?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Let me be very clear about what this is and what it isn't.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "What can you tell us?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "We are absolutely clear-eyed and we've been planning ourselves and with our partners, particularly in the region of Turkey and Israel and Jordan and others.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Do you have plans for those contingencies that would not involve boots on the ground?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "This military operation is focused on the objective of deterring and degrading the Syrian regime's ability to use chemical weapons.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Do you want regime change right now?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I think the mandate for this is very clear.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What gives you the mandate to do it alone?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "We're working through that right now.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "At this point, what do you think it's going to cost?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I don't have those figures at hand right now.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Which would be?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "That's a good one.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "I guest the first one should be that we shouldn't call Assad, Saddam, right?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Is that unusual that you wouldn't have heard that at this point?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, Nick, why don't you get it on that because, you know, frankly you have been following your work for a lot of years.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "And what nobody seems to be able to explain to any of us is how are these two things linked?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, I made a couple of thoughts.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes I do.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Neda, you have a question for us?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Are we really the country to take the moral high road on Assad's use of chemical weapons?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "And what's the endgame?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well that gets to the obvious question that we don't know why this is being done.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What about that part?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "I think anybody who thinks that American politician even one as experienced as John McCain has any deep understanding of the hatreds, the rivalries, the clan (ph) work violence, the religious conflicts that make a place like Syria operate is rejecting all the evidence we have over the last 15 years.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What is your take on that, Newt?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I don't think we do.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "So, Philip how do we know who to help?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well and I think you've seen now over the last several days, the President walk back from his original language, well it's not my red line, it's the international community's red line and it's Congress's red line, it's everybody's right.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Just because it may have been a political statement that was made, that was wise or unwise, why is the justification for it have to be bombing?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, depending on what we want to do.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Rick, what is the chance so this could be quick on the military level and then unpacking what happens with the fallout?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "100 percent and I think it's all right to decide our future or, you know, it's all right to decide our regime, it's not -- it's no one's business to decide.", "docId": "130905pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "So, Tom you're saying you support the Asaad regime?", "qSentId": 531}]